this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this is psyched i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next
with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line
to the new world after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother
ace to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down now he's racing down to level five
with the help of escaped prisoner buggy the clown i got the key to the treasure i got that jump off
my back and soon i'll be free i rob you got my revenge and you thanked me for it
stupid you can't chop me what do you think the chop chop fruit is for
strongest man in the prison poison man magellan appears
i busted out of myself to escape not to end up in an even worse hell than before
creepy but at least now i have this which puts me that much closer to finding captain john's
treasure all i have to do is find my way out of
okay let's go just tell me the way
what the hold on a second
it's a dead end
so level two huh
that's right they call it the wild beast hill and it's even worse than the crimson hill on level one
damn it don't run off with my head i can't catch up
anyway this floor is swimming with giant monsters that'll swallow you up in one bite
oh yeah wow
all right focus until i can find a way out of this dump
i gotta take advantage of straw hat any way i can
is that one of them there
you're kidding me it found us already
looks like a hippo to me yeah it does he's a lot smaller than a regular hippo that's really a wild beast
that's funny i always heard level two was full of big savage what the hell
awesome look little guy's pretty fast for a hippo
stop admiring it turn left quick
nice one you run
you run fast but you're not too hot when it comes to turning
oh hey are you sure it's all right for him to eat your body like that
yeah it's no big deal keep running i'll show you what a chop chop man can do
whoa how did you manage that
even if my body parts are chopped into tiny pieces i can still move them around however i want
that'll teach you stupid hippo
who is that the other guy standing there behind buggy
there's gotta be some way out of this crappy situation i can't just run around forever
what's wrong
i thought i saw something
maybe it was a bat
some kind of monster mantis
i think you're right way too big for a regular mantis
whoa he cuts like a champ
stop admiring the anime
if i get chopped up much more than this it's gonna be a big problem
he's cool you think we could be friends
what's wrong with you can't you see we're in danger
hey look at that i think you're stuck
maybe we should uh let's just go
so are these things really the wild beasts of hell
they just don't seem like that big of a deal to me
you're right they aren't as bad as i'd heard
everything up on level one was way more terrifying than this
maybe they're just called that to dissuade anyone from trying
why am i even here i didn't want to go to level two in the first
place i was trying to escape and leave you behind your bad luck everything that sucks
in my life is all your fault
what did you say something and what is this thing chasing us
from the looks of it i'd say it's the rarest kind of monster in existence
a snake born from a chicken egg a basilisk
that thing came out of a chicken
i said it was a monster didn't i these things shouldn't be allowed to live let alone run free
they eat people like snacks so they lock them up here where they can only eat criminals
what are you doing
i don't have time for this snake bird i'm gonna kick your ass
you're the one who's gonna get your ass kicked moron
hey wait a second now i can escape
i'll leave the rest to you sound good see you straw hat
attention jailers on level two attention we've identified the man with buggy the clown
it's straw hat luffy the straw hat luffy what's he doing in impel down
just capture them both immediately dead or alive it doesn't matter
let's go
what was that what happened
oh crap this cannot be good
it's getting hot well as the vice warden told you before the warden's office is located on level 4 which is known as the burning heat floor
aside from his office the whole floor is an inferno
there we finally arrived
well where is he where is this warden
warden magellan suffers from terrible digestive problems so he stays in the bathroom an average of ten hours a day seven days a week
of course he sleeps about eight hours each night so once you factor in meal times and breaks he only works about four hours a day
is that really enough time to do his job when the need arises he's the right man
oh we're in luck sounds like he's coming out
and i forgot to mention it before but the warden ate the venom venom fruit so he's a poison man
poison man
yes please be careful
excellent work in there warden you showed those vows who's boss sir
as always it was a rough battle in there you must be our guests i'm magellan the warden here
ah this room is too bright for the record i much prefer places that are dark cold and closed off just like my heart
stop being ridiculous now listen vice admiral mamunga and the warlord boa hancock are here on important business
and our time is short warden magellan
ah my apologies i have a bad case of the runs i'm afraid the poison soup i had for breakfast this morning isn't quite agreeing with me
well what do you expect it's poison
oh come on i'm a poison man i love poison it's just like the old saying goes poison kills poison i believe
well that's why you have venomous diarrhea
yes and i'm afraid that you have a venomous tongue hanyable
hurry up and retire so i can become warden
oopsie i mean uh please hurry and show our guests a fire fist
yeah right like that was a slip of the tongue
it saddens my heart to know that my colleague thinks so little of me
put these on
warden please be careful when you exhale your breath is poisonous gas are you trying to kill everyone
hey what the hell is so funny
sir you're right stupid vice warden
and i have the venomous tongue
fool you dare breathe your disgusting poison in the face of an empress how rude
she's stepping on me and i think i like it
lucky punk
vice warden you realize that's the warden's seat you're in
it'll be mine soon enough
we don't have time for this
yes this is the warden's office
hey don't answer my phone
oh no i'm dying
damn it i just wanted to be warden
retrieve an antidote for the vice warden
right
what's that
you say someone broke into the prison
absurd this is impelled down
no one has ever infiltrated its walls
our defenses are flawless how could we possibly allow this
it is indeed a travesty and it was on your watch warden
have they found us out transfer the video footage to my chambers warden
i was wondering would it be possible to see the prisoner now
sure let's go like right now warden wake up we kind of need you to deal with this
now that's odd it appears that we've lost contact with warden magellan i want to report on every level of this place sent to the jailers room and navy headquarters now i don't know why he's here and i have no clue what he might be up to but that guy who's wreaking so much havoc with buggy the clown on level two is definitely straw hat luffy something's up we lost contact with the jailers room on level two what
damn it this whole place is going to hell what's going on well don't give up just yet stay on the line until they reply got that sir jailers room on level two what's going on down there what's wrong
his fist it was huge
why the hell are you so small
cause i used their gear
takes care of him
there we go
i'm back
okie-dokie let's get moving
the god of salvation has descended into hell
he beat the basilisk
i saw it myself
yes
the monster is down
he got him
you did it
you guys are amazing
they destroyed the jailers room too
it's a miracle
there must be angels sent from heaven
i don't know who you two are but thank you
hey guys could you hand us those keys too they're for these cuffs in the doors
they're right there see them over there on the ground
what's he doing
come on we gotta get going
don't be in such a rush
we're supposed to be saving my brother
that straw hat luffy
what is he doing down here
he's not in a cell nor in a prison uniform
and it looks like he's on his way out of here
alright
an opportunity like this one simply won't happen again
it's now or never
as much as i thought otherwise
it seems heaven hasn't forsaken me just yet
hey boys
is this what you're looking for
yeah
give it to me
let us out here
hmm
now is that any way to ask someone for a favor
we're sorry
we're begging you
that was inexcusable
we apologize
hmm
what was that
i couldn't hear you
yes you could
what the heck are you doing
please sir
alright
you got it
one set of keys coming right up
compliments of captain buggy
accepted with gratitude
you're free
you're finally out of those damn cells
that's right now i ask you
what's the glorious name of the man who has given you your sweet freedom
it's captain buggy and we're in your debt forever
anybody talking bad about buggy's gonna answer to us
that's me
and don't you scum ever forget it
now
unlock the other cells
set everyone free
once these morons start breaking havoc on this place i'll finally have a chance to sneak out on my own
hey what the hell are you doing
done
good
it's my turn
put me down
back to the plan
stupid
lead me down to the next level
isn't there a hole like last time or something
how should i know this place is like a maze
you expect me to remember the details of every floor
find your own damn way to level three
thanks for everything captain buggy
i can smell freedom already
put me down
shut up
you said you'd lead me all the way down to level four and now you're gonna do it
i lied okay
i just wanted the treasure so i lied to get it
with all those prisoners free the chaos will be immeasurable
and when that happens i'll
wait what was that you lied
yeah
what are you idiots doing you're free this is your chance to race hell and get out of here
we uh we just remembered why we never tried to do that escape is impossible especially with those wild beasts running around
yeah dying is for the birds we're way better off in this set
okay i've changed my mind straw hat i'll show you the way to level three let's go
what but you just said you didn't know the way big nose
my nose is perfect how rude
i couldn't help but overhear you if you're having trouble on this floor i can help
is that so who are you
long time no sea straw hat luffy you helped me out without noticing how fortunate i am a man who always pays back his debts
do i know you
huh
wait it's the three hair
holy crap look at his hair
you just shut up
it's the three and it's on fire
candle
oh yeah this should be perfect
come
fill it
why just a little game of high and sea can you figure out which one is me
you're just another buffoon who acts on blind instinct and uses brute force to solve all his problems
i am a baroque works agent
every assignment that is given to me i see through to its end
come
stay
how do you know which one was me
hutch
oh yeah you were on the island with the giants right three
mr three you fool
fleet admiral we've just received an emergency report from impel down
huh what's going on now
tell me is it white beard
no sir straw hat luffy has infiltrated the prison
what straw hat what is he doing there
i thought bartholome ukuma had taken care of that little troublemaker
yes that's the same report that i had heard as well sir
but what bothers me even more than that is why a pirate would sneak into impel down
do you have any clue what he might be planning
sir
well regardless of what straw hats got up his sleeve it's the end of the road for him this time
that is to say he picked the wrong place to break into
impel down has successfully held hundreds of thousands of criminals over the years many of them notorious pirates with powers as fearsome as their reputations their defenses are legendary and they're prepared for almost any situation
of course it was the guards incompetence that allowed him to enter but either way straw hat will never leave that place alive
but either way straw hat will never leave that place alive
only one man has
really
been
twenty long years ago
he became the first and only person in the history of impel down to escape
a pirate named sheki
a golden lion
sheki
the golden lion
in the history of impel down only one man has ever managed to escape from its walls
his name is sheki
the golden lion
twenty years later in what we now know as the present the straw hats encounter a giant beetle and find themselves wrapped up in sheki's plans
on the next one piece
a special presentation related to the movie
a gold lion's ambition on the move
i'm gonna be king of the pirates
p.g D.P.
M.D.
m.D.
The Holiday
it's avelace
man